Jhal Jhal Hello
Hello one to our post market
analyst so in today's video we will
see some important updates of yesterday and
we will discuss
how the market can fit in this future because the tax
is expiry so it is important for you to watch this video till the end so
without any delay let
us start this video at no.
If we talk about today's updates then
Nifty is just below its all time high
and for the first time we are seeing it closing above 17500
you can see that I have given a
bank settlement here a the
closing of 3850 and today here it is
601 hi we can see in this so if we look at the current
scenario while withdrawing cash and
looking at the global market trend then
Nifty is 6050 on the features side
and Bank Nifty can be seen above 036 972
here so you should also
avoid doing research telling on this highway
because it is possible that if it reaches
17500 then we may see some off side in it tomorrow  If we
can find it, let's see
what are the labels that we can use for our test.
Superintendent Dr.
A. Sudheen. If we talk about today's Nifty
chart, then the soil projects with a drop of honey
at 75102.
After consolidating above 1750 for the last few periods, today
we can see a breakout of the side here due to volume. So,
they are here because today we have seen 820 tracking
above and
below 17500 because there has been a
exile in the cords here. After our tax,
an idiot support level from 17.18
cannot be formed here. If it
sustains 90% above this, then you
can take a scalp at 17500 and that too on the call side.
Tannin suppression equal can be done here.
Apart from this, Bank Nifty
also comes out of a consolidation zone today
and we finally
do it according to 3720 and here. If we
talk about the top of the half candle, then the last pin
and  I am also hungry for some profit in this,
but because it has given its closing with a little recovery, then
tomorrow when it reaches 3490,
you can see pressure on it. It is
clear once in the events open interest that the
call writing which is at 3712 right now, if tomorrow some
call riders
square off their positions and as
we have seen an all unwinding today, it becomes
clear once again that at
3700 you can see it improving from here,
which we will
talk about again here Indra Mani Kaul
contract and you can type such scalp in it,
who is responsible for this website, so let's
know which are those stocks which we are
considering for our test further. Considering
a nice today,
after putting in an important advance above the audio, we get to
see almost all the telecom stocks closed and from which
one stop this can be in the biggest profit,
whereas Bharti Airtel today held its top position.  It has
touched a new high right
above 730. If you look at the current lows,
if you do your cow in it, then you can
activate the internet on a father website here,
so 725 will remain our immortal, on which,
according to confirmation,
12541 will go up to 750. Apart from this, we will click as vitamin in this festival. The next stock is this is My Trip, and this too, after today's major offside, it is approaching just below its 52-week high. So, guys, 550 color stain here is
quite a question for this because
if it is successful in crossing today's above
bath here, then you can again go up to
550 and 560.
And before dying on the third topic,
in this video of Irfan, full mature
gambling. Subscribe and share this video as much as
possible because it gives us a lot of
motivation and you can also introduce a new way of
trading without such speculation to your friends.  The
third one is NTPC which was
again traded here today with an option
and if you look at it, the
stock has been consolidating below 120 for the last few periods
and because today it came to your side
and it has come to its roots, on its own and on the
other hand we have done it above 125, we
can set a reminder in it,
our stop will be ah
27408 plus and the stoploss here is
Candy Crush of ₹10 from the date,
this is only for those elements who are
feeling off, after this the last
stock is Jain Sir and it has also
consolidated below 4043 for the last few periods -
but if you look at it, there is a
very good police momentum in the stock in the last one week and
today the highest volume was due to Rekha Rani,
we can see that it crossed between itself and Hafiza, so
if this top opens above the daughter which happened yesterday again, then
you should look at it for at least ₹10
And if possible, you can
cancel your personal profit booking from 590,
they are above it, if you talk face to face, then
you can also see the situated organization Tilak in it, so that's all for
today's
video, if you have
not yet joined our Telegram channel, then
you will definitely find the link and details below,
and for more explosives, spring
and position updates, you can join
this group, your statistics in
section 2, friends, if you want to give a part of our
model portfolio, meeting and
demand, subscribe, join from
different, because there we
get some success in generating a good profit here every single day without any struggle, so we will
meet in the next video, till then,
thank you, so much has happened, see you next
month,
[Music]